export default data = [
  {
      question: "Bobby cared a lot about his _____ at home and asked his parents not to go through his things without his permission.",
      options: ["discipline","facility","privacy","representation"],
      correct_option: "privacy"
  },
  {
      question: "The new manager is a real gentleman. He is kind and humble, totally different from the former manager, who was _____ and bossy.",
      options: ["eager","liberal","mean","inferior"],
      correct_option: "mean"
  },
  {
      question: "The weather bureau _____ that the typhoon would bring strong winds and heavy rains, and warned everyone of the possible danger. ",
      options: ["conveyed","associated","interpreted","predicted"],
      correct_option: "predicted"
  },
  {
      question: "Different airlines have different _____ for carry-on luggage, but many international airlines limit a carry-on piece to 7 kilograms.",
      options: ["landmarks","restrictions","percentages","circumstances"],
      correct_option: "restrictions"
  },
  {
      question: "Many people were happy that the government had finally _____ Children’s Day as a national holiday.",
      options: ["appointed","declared","performed","involved"],
      correct_option: "declared"
  },
  {
      question: "To reach the goal of making her company a market leader, Michelle _____ a plan to open ten new stores around the country this year.",
      options: ["advised","occupied","proposed","recognized"],
      correct_option: "proposed"
  },
  {
      question: "Silence in some way is as _____ as speech. It can be used to show, for example, disagreement or lack of interest.",
      options: ["sociable","expressive","reasonable","objective"],
      correct_option: "expressive"
  },
  {
      question: "This TV program is designed for children, _____ for those under five. It contains no violence or strong language. ",
      options: ["particularly","sensibly","moderately","considerably"],
      correct_option: "particularly"
  },
  {
      question: "Tommy, please put away the toys in the box, or you might _____ on them and hurt yourself.",
      options: ["stumble","graze","navigate","dwell"],
      correct_option: "stumble"
  },
  {
      question: "The _____ costume party, held every September, is one of the biggest events of the school year.",
      options: ["initial","annual","evident","occasional"],
      correct_option: "annual"
  },
  {
      question: "In a job interview, attitude and personality are usually important _____ that influence the decision of the interviewers.",
      options: ["factors","outcomes","missions","identities"],
      correct_option: "factors"
  },
  {
      question: "The snow-capped mountain is described so _____ in the book that the scene seems to come alive in front of the reader’s eyes.",
      options: ["distantly","meaningfully","cheerfully","vividly"],
      correct_option: "vividly"
  },
  {
      question: "Surrounded by flowers blooming and birds _____ merrily, the Wangs had a good time hiking in the national park.",
      options: ["napping","scooping","flipping","chirping"],
      correct_option: "chirping"
  },
  {
      question: "It is essential for us to maintain constant _____ with our friends to ensure that we have someone to talk to in times of need.",
      options: ["benefit","contact","gesture","favor"],
      correct_option: "contact"
  },
  {
      question: "The young generation in this country has shown less interest in factory work and other _____ labor jobs, such as house construction and fruit picking.",
      options: ["causal","durable","manual","violent"],
      correct_option: "manual"
  },
]